getprivate.net 2016-03-09

# GetPrivate - Secure Free VPN

**Last Modified: October 19th, 2012**

This document describes what information is collected by us from any user of the GetPrivate VPN (collectively or individually "User(s)"), as well as our use and disclosure of that information.

**NOTE TO KIDS** : GETPRIVATE VPN IS NOT AVAILABLE TO PERSONS UNDER THE AGE OF 18. 

If you are under 18 years of age, please do not use GetPrivate VPN.

**OUR COMMITMENT TO USER PRIVACY:**  
GetPrivate does not collect any personally identifiable information on GetPrivate VPN. GetPrivate VPN automatically collects certain non-personally identifiable information from Users that is used in the aggregate only. GetPrivate does not collect, store, or share any permanent identifiers of Users, including IP addresses. Please note that GetPrivate VPN only enables privacy and encrypts user Internet sessions when it is turned ON. Having GetPrivate VPN on the desktop, without turning it ON does not do anything. Unless Users turn GetPrivate VPN ON and opt into the service, GetPrivate VPN will be completely idle.

**OUR COMMITMENT TO WEB SECURITY:**  
GetPrivate VPN encrypts every page visited by our Users, thus protecting communications between each User and the Internet. GetPrivate GetPrivate VPN employs certain physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of any information collected. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant that the safeguards will be uninterrupted or effective, or that any information you transmit to GetPrivate VPN will remain secure, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, GetPrivate employs certain techniques and technologies to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. If GetPrivate learns of a security systems breach, we may post a notice on the GetPrivate website to notify Users. Please note that GetPrivate VPN helps secure your Internet session, not your computer. GetPrivate VPN does not protect your computer from viruses or malware. We recommend getting anti-virus/anti-malware solutions from one of our reputable partners in order to also help secure your computer.

**THE INFORMATION GETPRIVATE VPN COLLECTS:**  
"Automatically Collected" Information. When you use the GetPrivate VPN, some information may be automatically recorded using different types of proprietary technology. The automatically-collected information does not identify a User personally, and GetPrivate only uses the automatically collected information for various purposes, including but not limited to monitoring of the traffic statistics, VPN usage by time, internet speed and so on.

**THE WAY GETPRIVATE USES INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM GETPRIVATE VPN:**  
GetPrivate may use automatically-collected information in the aggregate to monitor the advertisements displayed on the GetPrivate VPN, and for purposes of research or analysis. Please note that by having GetPrivate VPN on your computer, but not turned on, no information is collected by GetPrivate. Anonymous web information may only be collected when you turn GetPrivate VPN ON.

**WHEN GETPRIVATE DISCLOSES INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM GETPRIVATE VPN:**  
GetPrivate may share anonymous data with a variety of third parties, including its affiliates, advertisers, and other current and prospective business partners. GetPrivate may use anonymous data collected for website administration, advertising, and promotional purposes, and may share such information with various affiliated and unaffiliated entities for such purposes.  
GetPrivate may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess technology that allows GetPrivate to customize the advertising and marketing messages Users receive while using the GetPrivate VPN, and those outside companies may have access to anonymous data that was collected from GetPrivate VPN users.  
GetPrivate may disclose automatically collected and other aggregate non-personally-identifiable information with interested third parties to assist such parties in understanding the usage, viewing, and demographic patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the GetPrivate VPN.

**THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISERS, LINKS TO OTHER SITES ON THE GETPRIVATE VPN:**  
GetPrivate allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within GetPrivate VPN. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links. Any third parties including advertisers may automatically receive the virtual IP Address assigned by GetPrivate. Your original IP address will not be collected or provided to any third parties by GetPrivate. Advertisers may also use other technologies (such as cookies, javascript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize their advertising content. GetPrivate's GetPrivate VPN Privacy Notice does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or other web sites visited by Users. Please note that this Privacy Notice will not apply to your activities or any information you disclose while using any third-party products or services or otherwise interacting with third parties. How third parties handle and use your personal information related to their sites and services is governed by their security, privacy and other policies, if any, and not this Privacy Notice. GetPrivate has no responsibility for any third party's policies, or any third party's compliance with them. Anyone may opt out of the cookies as directed by NAI opt-out page, which is currently located at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp 

**CHANGES AND UPDATES TO THIS GETPRIVATE VPN PRIVACY NOTICE:**  
This GetPrivate VPN Privacy Notice may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the "last modified" notice above. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of the GetPrivate VPN constitutes your agreement to this GetPrivate VPN Privacy Notice and any future revisions.

**GETPRIVATE CONTACT INFORMATION:**  
Please contact GetPrivate with any questions or comments about this GetPrivate VPN Privacy Notice at info@getprivate.net. Please note that if you contact GetPrivate, you will be disclosing your personal information, and the use of such personal information will be governed by the GetPrivate Privacy Policy.
